[
  {
    "exhibitName": "Publix",
    "activityName": "Cultural Foods",
    "easy": {
      "question": "How many ingredients did you need to make the Hispanic meal?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "3", "5", "1", "7"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "3"
    },
    "medium": {
      "question": "Which one of these did we not use in the Hispanic recipe?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Rice", "Soup", "Tomato", "Carrots"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Tomato"
    },
    "hard": {
      "question": "Name one of the ingredients from the Hispanic meal in Spanish",
      "questionType": "fill in",
      "correctAnswers": ["arroz", "zanahoria", "sopa"]
    }
  },
  {
    "exhibitName": "Publix",
    "activityName": "Nutrition",
    "easy": {
      "question": "Which of these is not one of the five main food groups?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Vegetables", "Fruits", "Candy", "Dairy"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Candy"
    },
    "medium": {
      "question": "Which of these food types should you eat most of during a typical day?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Dairy", "Vegetables", "Protein", "Fruits"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Vegetables"
    },
    "hard": {
      "question": "Name one of the five main food group.",
      "questionType": "fill in",
      "correctAnswers": ["Fruits", "Vegetables", "Protein", "Dairy"]
    }
  },
  {
    "exhibitName": "Publix",
    "activityName": "Money",
    "easy": {
      "question": "How much money did you start with to buy supplies?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "$30", "$20", "$5", "$10"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "$10"
    },
    "medium": {
      "question": "You started with $10 to buy supplies. You bought an item for $3. How much do you have left?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "$7", "$3", "$5", "$1"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "$7"
    },
    "hard": {
      "question": "You started with $10 to buy supplies. You bought an item for $3. How much do you have left?",
      "questionType": "fill in",
      "correctAnswers": ["$3", "3"]
    }
  },
  {
    "exhibitName": "Publix",
    "activityName": "Sorting",
    "easy": {
      "question": "Which of these items is shortest?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Carton of milk", "Muffin", "Cereal", "Can of tomatoes"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Muffin"
    },
    "medium": {
      "question": "Which list is sorted correctly, from shortest to tallest?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Cereal box, can of tomatoes, muffin", "Muffin, can of tomatoes, cereal box", "Can of tomatoes, cereal box, muffin", "Muffin, cereal box, can of tomatoes"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Muffin, can of tomatoes, cereal box"
    },
    "hard": {
      "question": "What is the opposite of tall?",
      "questionType": "fill in",
      "correctAnswers": ["short"]
    }
  },
  {
    "exhibitName": "Publix",
    "activityName": "Letters",
    "easy": {
      "question": "Which of these foods starts with the same letter as Robot?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Pear", "Banana", "Orange ", "Rice"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Rice"
    },
    "medium": {
      "question": "Which food starts with the first letter of the alphabet?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Pears", "Bread", "Spaghetti", "Apples"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Apples"
    },
    "hard": {
      "question": "What letter does Eggplant start with?",
      "questionType": "fill in",
      "correctAnswers": ["e"]
    }
  },
  {
    "exhibitName": "Medical and Vet",
    "activityName": "Bones",
    "easy": {
      "question": "What animal needed to get an X-Ray at the vet?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Cat", "Snake", "Dog", "Bat"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Dog"
    },
    "medium": {
      "question": "Which of these animals is the largest?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Cat", "Snake", "Dog", "Bat"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Dog"
    },
    "hard": {
      "question": "What did the dog have to get when he went to the vet?",
      "questionType": "fill in",
      "correctAnswers": ["x-ray", "xray"]
    }
  },
  {
    "exhibitName": "Medical and Vet",
    "activityName": "Eating the Rainbow",
    "easy": {
      "question": "What can a person with Celiac disease not eat?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Bread or grains", "Dairy", "Fruit", "Protein"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Bread or grains"
    },
    "medium": {
      "question": "This disease occurs when the person has an allergic reaction to bread or grains.",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Celiac disease", "Lactose intolerance", "Peanut allergy", "Tree nut allergies"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Celiac disease"
    },
    "hard": {
      "question": "What can a person with Celiac disease not eat?",
      "questionType": "fill in",
      "correctAnswers": ["Bread", "grain "]
    }
  },
  {
    "exhibitName": "Medical and Vet",
    "activityName": "Going to the Doctor",
    "easy": {
      "question": "What body part is affected when it hurts to swallow?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Stomach", "Head", "Throat", "Nose"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Throat"
    },
    "medium": {
      "question": "The human body has a system that is composed of all of our bones that is called the ___",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Skeletal system", "Nervous System", "Muscular System", "Digestive System"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Skeletal system"
    },
    "hard": {
      "question": "What body part is affected when it hurts to swallow?",
      "questionType": "fill in",
      "correctAnswers": ["Throat"]
    }
  },
  {
    "exhibitName": "Outback/Carraba's",
    "activityName": "Make Me a Pizza",
    "easy": {
      "question": "What's the first ingredient that you put on the pizza?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Cheese", "Pepperoni", "Sauce", "Peppers"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Sauce"
    },
    "medium": {
      "question": "If you put 2 pieces of pepperoni and 1 green pepper, how many ingredients are on the pizza?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "3", "1", "4", "2"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "3"
    },
    "hard": {
      "question": "If you put 2 pieces of pepperoni and 1 green pepper, how many ingredients are on the pizza?",
      "questionType": "fill in",
      "correctAnswers": ["3", "three"]
    }
  },
  {
    "exhibitName": "Outback/Carraba's",
    "activityName": "Advanced Pizza Making (8-11 year olds)",
    "easy": {
      "question": "You and three friends each want two pizzas. How many pizzas will you have total?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "4", "8", "6", "10"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "8"
    },
    "medium": {
      "question": "If you cut a pizza into four slices and take one piece, how much of the pizza did you take?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "1/3", "1/2", "1/4", "1/8"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "1/4"
    },
    "hard": {
      "question": "If you cut a pizza into four slices and take one piece, how much of the pizza did you take?",
      "questionType": "fill in",
      "correctAnswers": ["1/4"]
    }
  },
  {
    "exhibitName": "Outback/Carraba's",
    "activityName": "Order up!",
    "easy": {
      "question": "What does a server at a restaurant not do?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Cook the food", "Take the orders", "Deliver the food", "Remember the orders"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Cook the food"
    },
    "medium": {
      "question": "What did the family order from Outback?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "One ham sandwich", "One turkey sandwich", "One cheese sandwich and one turkey sandwich", "One cheese sandwich and two ham sandwiches"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "One cheese sandwich and two ham sandwiches"
    },
    "hard": {
      "question": "How many sandwiches did the family at Outback order?",
      "questionType": "fill in",
      "correctAnswers": ["3", "three"]
    }
  },
  {
    "exhibitName": "Outback/Carraba's",
    "activityName": "I'm Here to Help",
    "easy": {
      "question": "How much was the bill for the family who couldn't afford their meals?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "$10", "$20", "$30", "$40"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "$20"
    },
    "medium": {
      "question": "How much money did the family who couldn't pay their bill need to completely pay their bill?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "$1", "$5", "$10", "$15"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "$5"
    },
    "hard": {
      "question": "How much money did the family who couldn't pay their bill need to completely pay the bill?",
      "questionType": "fill in",
      "correctAnswers": ["$5", "5"]
    }
  },
  {
    "exhibitName": "Outback/Carraba's",
    "activityName": "Planning a Party",
    "easy": {
      "question": "How many steps are there when planning a party?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "6", "8", "4", "5"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "6"
    },
    "medium": {
      "question": "What is the first step in planning a party?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Set-up decorations", "Order food", "Make the guest list", "Buy a present"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Make the guest list"
    },
    "hard": {
      "question": "How many steps are there when planning a party?",
      "questionType": "fill in",
      "correctAnswers": ["6", "six"]
    }
  },
  {
    "exhibitName": "Fire Station",
    "activityName": "Fire Fighter!",
    "easy": {
      "question": "How many steps are there in a fire drill?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "5", "7", "12", "3"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "7"
    },
    "medium": {
      "question": "What is the first step for a fire fighter in a fire drill?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Go down the pole", "Arrive at the scene", "Put out the fire", "Look for anyone in danger"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Go down the pole"
    },
    "hard": {
      "question": "How many steps are in a fire drill?",
      "questionType": "fill in",
      "correctAnswers": ["7", "seven"]
    }
  },
  {
    "exhibitName": "Art",
    "activityName": "Shall We Dance?",
    "easy": {
      "question": "",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "", "", "", ""
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : ""
    },
    "medium": {
      "question": "",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "", "", "", ""
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : ""
    },
    "hard": {
      "question": "",
      "questionType": "fill in",
      "correctAnswers": ["", "", "", ""]
    }
  },
  {
    "exhibitName": "Art",
    "activityName": "Kaleidoscope",
    "easy": {
      "question": "If you have a pink circle and Malcolm, who can't see your circle, has a purple circle, does Malcolm think your circle is purple?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Yes", "No"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Yes"
    },
    "medium": {
      "question": "If you have a pink circle and Malcolm, who can't see your circle, has a purple circle, what color does Malcolm think your circle is?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Pink", "Blue", "Purple", "Orange"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Purple"
    },
    "hard": {
      "question": "If you have a pink circle and Malcolm, who can't see your circle, has a purple circle, does Malcolm think your circle is purple?",
      "questionType": "fill in",
      "correctAnswers": ["Yes"]
    }
  },
  {
    "exhibitName": "Art",
    "activityName": "The Case of the Missing Letter",
    "easy": {
      "question": "Which letter completes this word: C_W",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "O", "U", "E", "A"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "O"
    },
    "medium": {
      "question": "Which letter completes this word: RO_OT",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "C", "B", "P", "N"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "B"
    },
    "hard": {
      "question": "What letter completes this word: WA_ER?",
      "questionType": "fill in",
      "correctAnswers": ["T"]
    }
  },
  {
    "exhibitName": "Art",
    "activityName": "How the Mind Wanders",
    "easy": {
      "question": "",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "", "", "", ""
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : ""
    },
    "medium": {
      "question": "",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "", "", "", ""
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : ""
    },
    "hard": {
      "question": "",
      "questionType": "fill in",
      "correctAnswers": ["", "", "", ""]
    }
  },
  {
    "exhibitName": "Art",
    "activityName": "Time to Draw!",
    "easy": {
      "question": "",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "", "", "", ""
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : ""
    },
    "medium": {
      "question": "",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "", "", "", ""
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : ""
    },
    "hard": {
      "question": "",
      "questionType": "fill in",
      "correctAnswers": ["", "", "", ""]
    }
  },
  {
    "exhibitName": "Get Moving",
    "activityName": "Surely You're Joking",
    "easy": {
      "question": "Complete the sentence: The _____ is a plane.",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Turtle", "Parrot", "Dog", "Mouse"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Parrot"
    },
    "medium": {
      "question": "Complete the sentence: The _____ is a tree.",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Giraffe", "Fish", "Mouse", "Snail"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Giraffe"
    },
    "hard": {
      "question": "Complete the sentence: The ____ is a plane.",
      "questionType": "fill in",
      "correctAnswers": ["Parrot"]
    }
  },
  {
    "exhibitName": "Get Moving",
    "activityName": "Who is faster?",
    "easy": {
      "question": "What animal below was the slowest at the races?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Dog", "Rabbit", "Turtle", "Parrot"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Turtle"
    },
    "medium": {
      "question": "What animal below was faster than a turtle but slower than a rabbit at the races?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Parrot", "Dog", "Cat", "Hamster"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Dog"
    },
    "hard": {
      "question": "What animal was fastest at the races?",
      "questionType": "fill in",
      "correctAnswers": ["Parrot"]
    }
  },
  {
    "exhibitName": "Get Moving",
    "activityName": "At the Races",
    "easy": {
      "question": "Which animal did Malcolm the Robot run as fast as?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Dog", "Rabbit", "Parrot", "Turtle"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Dog"
    },
    "medium": {
      "question": "Which animal beat Malcolm the Robot in the race?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Frog", "Turtle", "Parrot", "Dog"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Parrot"
    },
    "hard": {
      "question": "Which animal did Malcolm the Robot run as fast as?",
      "questionType": "fill in",
      "correctAnswers": ["Dog"]
    }
  },
  {
    "exhibitName": "Get Moving",
    "activityName": "How High?",
    "easy": {
      "question": "How many inches are in one foot?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "10", "12", "6", "1"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "12"
    },
    "medium": {
      "question": "How tall is the average 4 to 6 year old child?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "1 to 2 feet", "10 to 20 inches", "37 to 42 inches", "75 to 100 inches"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "37 to 42 inches"
    },
    "hard": {
      "question": "How many inches are in one foot?",
      "questionType": "fill in",
      "correctAnswers": ["12", "twelve"]
    }
  },
  {
    "exhibitName": "Get Moving",
    "activityName": "How Strong?",
    "easy": {
      "question": "What color were the balls on the How High machine?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Yellow", "Green", "Blue", "Red"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Red"
    },
    "medium": {
      "question": "How many bars could a frog turn on with a really good jump?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "5", "3", "1", "7"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "5"
    },
    "hard": {
      "question": "How many red bars could a frog turn on with a really good jump?",
      "questionType": "fill in",
      "correctAnswers": ["5", "five"]
    }
  },
  {
    "exhibitName": "Get Moving",
    "activityName": "Stop that Ball!",
    "easy": {
      "question": "What type of item were you trying to keep out of the net?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Hockey Puck", "Soccer Ball", "Baseball", "Volleyball"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Soccer Ball"
    },
    "medium": {
      "question": "The two sides of your body are sometimes referred to as these two directions.",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Right and wrong", "Right and left", "East and west", "Up and down"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Right and left"
    },
    "hard": {
      "question": "What type of items were you trying to keep out of the net?",
      "questionType": "fill in",
      "correctAnswers": ["Soccer ball", "hockey puck"]
    }
  },
  {
    "exhibitName": "Invention Zone",
    "activityName": "Lego Activity-egocentrism and motor skills",
    "easy": {
      "question": "If you show Malcolm the Robot that there are three balls in a green bag and then make him close his eyes while you take the balls out, will he know that you took the balls out of the bag?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Yes", "No"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Yes"
    },
    "medium": {
      "question": "If you show Malcolm the Robot that there are three balls in a green bag and then make him close his eyes while you take the balls out, where will he thinks the balls are when he opens his eyes?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "In the bag", "Outside of the bag"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "In the bag"
    },
    "hard": {
      "question": "If you show Malcolm the Robot that there are three balls in a bag and then make him close his eyes while you add a ball, how many balls will he think there are when he opens his eyes?",
      "questionType": "fill in",
      "correctAnswers": ["3", "three"]
    }
  },
  {
    "exhibitName": "Invention Zone",
    "activityName": "Where will it go?",
    "easy": {
      "question": "What happens when the vacuum sucks up the ball?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "It flies out the top", "It doesn't move", "It goes down the pipe"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "It flies out the top"
    },
    "medium": {
      "question": "Where does the ball land after it flies out of the vacuum?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "In the cylinder", "On the ground", "On the other side of the room"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : ""
    },
    "hard": {
      "question": "What is the machine called that sucks up the ball?",
      "questionType": "fill in",
      "correctAnswers": ["Vacuum"]
    }
  },
  {
    "exhibitName": "Invention Zone",
    "activityName": "Twinkle Star Theater",
    "easy": {
      "question": "",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "", "", "", ""
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : ""
    },
    "medium": {
      "question": "",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "", "", "", ""
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : ""
    },
    "hard": {
      "question": "",
      "questionType": "fill in",
      "correctAnswers": ["", "", "", ""]
    }
  },
  {
    "exhibitName": "Water Area",
    "activityName": "Piloting a Boat",
    "easy": {
      "question": "",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "", "", "", ""
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : ""
    },
    "medium": {
      "question": "",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "", "", "", ""
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : ""
    },
    "hard": {
      "question": "",
      "questionType": "fill in",
      "correctAnswers": ["", "", "", ""]
    }
  },
  {
    "exhibitName": "Water Area",
    "activityName": "Hidden Treasure",
    "easy": {
      "question": "Gasparilla Island is named after which famous pirate?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "John Gasp", "Rafael Pari", "Jose Gaspar", "Roberto Gaso"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Jose Gaspar"
    },
    "medium": {
      "question": "What was Jose Gaspar's nickname?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "The Buccaneering Pirate", "The last of the Buccaneers", "The last of the pirates of Tampa Bay", "The Great Gasparilla"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "The last of the Buccaneers"
    },
    "hard": {
      "question": "Gasparilla Island was named after which famous pirate?",
      "questionType": "fill in",
      "correctAnswers": ["Jose Gaspar", "Gaspar"]
    }
  },
  {
    "exhibitName": "Water Area",
    "activityName": "Sailing, Sailing",
    "easy": {
      "question": "In what sea is Cozumel located?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Caribbean Sea", "Dead Sea", "Aegean Sea", "Mediterranean Sea"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Caribbean Sea"
    },
    "medium": {
      "question": "What does radar stand for?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Really Awesome DARting", "RAdio Detecting and Ranging", "Readily ADding Arches", "RAdio Direction AnywheRe"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "RAdio Detecting and Ranging "
    },
    "hard": {
      "question": "Cozumel is located in which sea?",
      "questionType": "fill in",
      "correctAnswers": ["Caribbean"]
    }
  },
  {
    "exhibitName": "Water Area",
    "activityName": "Ahoy, There!",
    "easy": {
      "question": "What part of the telescope do you look through to see objects far away?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Control Handle", "Focuser", "Mount", "Eyepiece "
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Eyepiece "
    },
    "medium": {
      "question": "Where are the lenses of the telescope located?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Optical tubes", "Mount", "Stand", "Control Handle"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Optical tubes"
    },
    "hard": {
      "question": "What part of the telescope do you look through to see objects far away?",
      "questionType": "fill in",
      "correctAnswers": ["Eyepiece"]
    }
  },
  {
    "exhibitName": "Water Area",
    "activityName": "What's Down There?",
    "easy": {
      "question": "What object might be best to take pictures underwater?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Underwater binoculars", "Underwater phone", "Underwater camera", "Underwater xBox"
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Underwater camera"
    },
    "medium": {
      "question": "What object might be best to take pictures underwater?",
      "questionType": "multiple choice",
      "possibleAnswers": [
        "Underwater binoculars", "Underwater camera", "Underwater phone", "Underwater xBox "
      ],
      "correctAnswer" : "Underwater camera"
    },
    "hard": {
      "question": "An underwater version of one of these is best for taking pictures underwater.",
      "questionType": "fill in",
      "correctAnswers": ["Camera"]
    }
  }
]
